<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Untitled RSS Feed]]></title><description><![CDATA[Untitled RSS Feed]]></description><link>https://joelcbailey.github.io</link><generator>RSS for Node</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2017 18:13:47 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://joelcbailey.github.io/rss/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><ttl>60</ttl><item><title><![CDATA[Z-Flex Deck Review (for all levels of experience)]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div id="preamble">
<div class="sectionbody">
<div class="paragraph">
<p>I&#8217;ve been riding my Z-Flex Original Z deck for about 9 months now and it has lasted me very well.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Z-flex is a 1976 company and normally focus on cruisers like the <a href="http://www.zflex.com/uk/catalog/product/view/id/3471/s/delirium-cruiser-green/">Z-Flex delirium green cruiser</a> or pool/bowl made boards like the <a href="http://www.zflex.com/uk/catalog/product/view/id/2316/s/master-crafted-eric-dressen-8-5/">Master Crafter Eric Dressen</a> but they have made a few street/transition decks like the <a href="http://www.zflex.com/uk/catalog/product/view/id/992/s/after-hours-rise-deck/">Rise Deck</a></p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>I bought the Z-Flex Original Z from my local skateshop called <a href="http://www.theskateshop.co.uk/">The Skateshop</a> (based in Poole).</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect1">
<h2 id="_pop_and_tail">Pop and Tail</h2>
<div class="sectionbody">
<div class="paragraph">
<p>So, this board has good pop that it retains for a good few months since I like to do tailslides I a have worn down the tail quite a bit quicker than normal, but this deck had survied it for again a good few months, this being said i didn&#8217;t even think of needing a new board till now because of the chips and the new shaped tail! 😂</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect1">
<h2 id="_snaps_and_cracks">Snaps and Cracks</h2>
<div class="sectionbody">
<div class="paragraph">
<p>The Original Z has not snapped and has no cracks! If I was to be doing lip slides and other tricks like that, it will most probably crack though	 (you will find that it will crack like this with most deck brands). When you stand on the board it feels great and has a flexible bendy feel but still feels firm and strong. For beginner skaters this board is perfect and you&#8217;ll have a fun time skating it.</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect1">
<h2 id="_rating_for_each_level_of_experience">Rating for each level of experience</h2>
<div class="sectionbody">
<div class="ulist">
<ul>
<li>
<p>No experience - really good choice. But, if you&#8217;re a complete beginner and your looking for a cheaper option as your first deck (but still easy to learn on), take a look at these decks:  <a href="https://www.skatehut.co.uk/skateboards/complete_skateboards/+enuff?gclid=CKP8_djX8NUCFeGw7QodSiMANQ">enuff skateboards</a>.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Beginner - this is probably going to be your second deck and you&#8217;re looking for a new set up. It&#8217;s the perfect time to consider the Z-Flex board and you&#8217;ll find that you will progress a lot!</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Intermediate - a really good time to get one and will be really fun to ride but at this stage it&#8217;ll be down to personal preference</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Expert - personal preference is all I need to say, at this stage you will know what deck you like.</p>
</li>
</ul>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Here are a few pictures of my Z-Flex Original Z new and at nine months old:</p>
</div>
<div class="imageblock">
<div class="content">
<img src="https://joelcbailey.github.io/images/IMG_8277.JPG" alt="IMG 8277.JPG">
</div>
</div>
<div class="imageblock">
<div class="content">
<img src="https://joelcbailey.github.io/images/IMG_8382.JPG" alt="IMG 8382.JPG">
</div>
</div>
<div class="imageblock">
<div class="content">
<img src="https://joelcbailey.github.io/images/IMG_8372.JPG" alt="IMG 8372.JPG">
</div>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>If you are looking for a new set up or deck <a href="http://www.theskateshop.co.uk/">the skate shop</a> is a great place to go with its wide range of skateboards.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Also remember that most brands keep the same shape for there decks so the origal Z is the same shape as most zflex boards <strong>for this sytyle of deck</strong> bur just a different pattern</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>How useful did you find this review? Please tell me <a href="https://strawpoll.com/fc4ywhra">here</a>.</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>]]></description><link>https://joelcbailey.github.io/2017/08/24/Z-Flex-Deck-Review-for-all-levels-of-experience.html</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://joelcbailey.github.io/2017/08/24/Z-Flex-Deck-Review-for-all-levels-of-experience.html</guid><category><![CDATA[skateboard_decks]]></category><category><![CDATA[Z-Flex]]></category><category><![CDATA[reviews]]></category><pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2017 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>